A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing and New York University, Nurses Improving Care for Healthsystem Elders (NICHE), Series 9 FA1721
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing and New York University, Nurses Improving Care for Healthsystem Elders (NICHE), 1997-2006; 9; 52.57 Cubic Feet
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 2, 105911-105973 (Box 14)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 2, 105974-106049 (Box 14)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 2, 106050-106117 (Box 14)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 2, 106118-106233 (Box 14)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3, 105857-105910 (Box 14)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3, 105911-105973 (Box 14)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3, 105974-106049 (Box 14)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3, 106050-106117 (Box 14)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3, 106118-106233 (Box 14)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 4, 105857-105910 (Box 15)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 4, 105911-105973 (Box 15)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 4, 105974-106049 (Box 15)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 4, 106050-106117 (Box 15)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 4, 106118-106233 (Box 15)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 105857-105910 (Box 15)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 105911-105973 (Box 15)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 105974-106049 (Box 15)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 106050-106117 (Box 15)
  - OSF St. Francis Medical Center, Providence, St. Vincent, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 106118-106233 (Box 15)
  - Providence Milwaukie Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 100084-100261 (Box 15)
  - Providence Milwaukie Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 100084-100261 (Box 15)
  - Providence Milwaukie Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 100084-100261 (Box 15)
  - Providence Milwaukie Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 100084-100261 (Box 15)
  - Providence Milwaukie Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 100084-100261 (Box 15)
  - Providence Milwaukie Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 100262-100315 (Box 15)
  - Providence Milwaukie Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 100262-100315 (Box 15)
  - Providence Milwaukie Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 100262-100315 (Box 15)
  - Providence Milwaukie Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 100262-100315 (Box 15)
  - Providence Milwaukie Hospital, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 100262-100315 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 100004-100077 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 100004-100077 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 100004-100077 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 100004-100077 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 100004-100077 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 100079-100352 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 100079-100352 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 100079-100352 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 100079-100352 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 100079-100352 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 100354-100384 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 100354-100384 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 100354-100384 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 100354-100384 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 100354-100384 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 100385-100400 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 100385-100400 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 100385-100400 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 100385-100400 (Box 15)
  - Providence Portland Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 100385-100400 (Box 15)
  - Providence St. Vincent Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1, 100104-100200 (Box 15)
  - Providence St. Vincent Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2, 100104-100200 (Box 15)
  - Providence St. Vincent Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3, 100104-100200 (Box 15)
  - Providence St. Vincent Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4, 100104-100200 (Box 15)
  - Providence St. Vincent Medical Center, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5, 100104-100200 (Box 15)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 1700-1722, 2902-2963 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 1700-1722, 2902-2963 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 1700-1722, 2902-2963 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 2964-2999, 7300-7314 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 2964-2999, 7300-7314 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 2964-2999, 7300-7314 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 7315-7381 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 7315-7381 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 7315-7381 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 7382-9917 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 7382-9917 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 7382-9917 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 9918-9979 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 9918-9979 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 9918-9979 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 9980-9995 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 9980-9995 (Box 16)
  - Morton Plant Mease Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 9980-9995 (Box 16)
  - Mountainview, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 1-2, 21327-27598 (Box 16)
  - Mt. Sinai, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 104136 (Box 16)
  - Mt. Sinai, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 103001-103999 (Box 16)
  - Mt. Sinai, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 101001 (Box 16)
  - Mt. Sinai, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 101334-101674 (Box 16)
  - Mt. Sinai, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 103640-104136 (Box 16)
  - Mt. Sinai, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4, 110990-111145 (Box 16)
  - Mt. Sinai, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4, 101334-101674 (Box 16)
  - Mt. Sinai, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4, 103640-104136 (Box 16)
  - Mt. Sinai, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5, 101334-101674 (Box 16)
  - Mt. Sinai, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5, 103645-104136 (Box 16)
  - New Rochelle Hospital Medical Center, Sound Shore, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 702-891 (Box 17)
  - New Rochelle Hospital Medical Center, Sound Shore, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 702-891 (Box 17)
  - New Rochelle Hospital Medical Center, Sound Shore, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 702-891 (Box 17)
  - New Rochelle Hospital Medical Center, Sound Shore, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 892-1005 (Box 17)
  - New Rochelle Hospital Medical Center, Sound Shore, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 892-1005 (Box 17)
  - New Rochelle Hospital Medical Center, Sound Shore, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 892-1005 (Box 17)
  - New Rochelle Hospital Medical Center, Sound Shore, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 1009-1130 (Box 17)
  - New Rochelle Hospital Medical Center, Sound Shore, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 1009-1130 (Box 17)
  - New Rochelle Hospital Medical Center, Sound Shore, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 1009-1130 (Box 17)
  - New Rochelle Hospital Medical Center, Sound Shore, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 1135-1199 (Box 17)
  - New Rochelle Hospital Medical Center, Sound Shore, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 1135-1199 (Box 17)
  - New Rochelle Hospital Medical Center, Sound Shore, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 1135-1199 (Box 17)
  - North Iowa, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 1-85 (Box 17)
  - North Iowa, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 1-85 (Box 17)
  - North Iowa, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 1-85 (Box 17)
  - North Iowa, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 86-197 (Box 17)
  - North Iowa, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 86-197 (Box 17)
  - North Iowa, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 86-197 (Box 17)
  - Trinitas Hospital, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1 (Box 17)
  - Trinitas Hospital, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2 (Box 17)
  - Trinitas Hospital, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3 (Box 17)
  - Trinitas Hospital, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4 (Box 17)
  - Trinitas Hospital, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5 (Box 17)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 2001-2138 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 2001-2138 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 2001-2138 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 2140-2255 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 2140-2255 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 2140-2255 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 6008-6037 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 6008-6037 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 6008-6037 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 6401-6431 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 6401-6431 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 6401-6431 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 2256-2456 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 2256-2456 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 2256-2456 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 2457-2499 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Medical Center, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 2457-2499 (Box 18)
  - Tucson Hospital, University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Etc., Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 2457-2499 (Box 18)
  - UC (University of California) Davis, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 4504-4668 (Box 18)
  - UC (University of California Davis, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 4504-4668 (Box 18)
  - UC (University of California Davis, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 4504-4668 (Box 18)
  - UC (University of California Davis, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 4671-4759 (Box 18)
  - UC (University of California Davis, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 4671-4759 (Box 18)
  - UC (University of California Davis, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 4671-4759 (Box 18)
  - UC (University of California Davis, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 4760-4900 (Box 18)
  - UC (University of California Davis, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4, 4760-4900 (Box 18)
  - UC (University of California Davis, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5, 4760-4900 (Box 18)
  - UC (University of California Davis, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 4901-5034 (Box 18)